[Music]
Hey, you two are still outside, I haven't
kept you inside. Lefty, he's not
saying much. Let him go. Righty, he's round. He doesn't know what
fitness is. Come on, talk to me.
I thought it was Diwali time, but there's
no time for goodness. Hey, Laddu, should I
celebrate your Diwali? Leave it now.
Anyway, we have to suffer because of this.
Our band will play after Diwali.
Hey, Pual Kids, no problem, friend.
You guys will meet only after Diwali.
Happy Diwali. Yes, hey, what is he doing? Look, how yummy, look, friend. Hey,
leave them.
Look at me, look at me, look at me. Hey, friend, a
corn has sat on you. Happy Diwali to the corn too.
Now fly away, friend. This brother will celebrate a
healthy Diwali by flaunting his sports shoes.
Whom will you make win this Diwali? Do the difficult one?